<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Something New</title>
    <link>https://kidonchu.github.io/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Something New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 22:44:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kidonchu.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Carving</title>
      <link>https://kidonchu.github.io/post/pumkin-carving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 22:44:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kidonchu.github.io/post/pumkin-carving/</guid>
      <description>




    
    
        
        
        
            
        
        
            
        
    

    
    
    

    
    




    
    
        
    


    

    
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;image center-image&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&#34;https://kidonchu.github.io/img/pumpkin-carving/halloween.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;halloween pumpkin carving&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s around that time of the year. Zombies arise from the dead, vampires wake up from their long
dream in coffins, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt4574334/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Stranger
Things&lt;/a&gt; start to happen in a house, deep in the forest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;Halloween!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, I did not celebrate Halloweens to the fullest. I often walked around without any costume, watching
what others had become. But nothing more than that. This year, I want to try something different,
&lt;em&gt;something new&lt;/em&gt;. Instead of being an observer, I want to enjoy the spirit of Halloween as much as
possible; all starting with, Pumpkin Carving!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-ready&#34;&gt;Getting ready&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I need to carve a pumpkin?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pumpkin&lt;/strong&gt;: Pretty one with consistent color all around&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carving knives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lights&lt;/strong&gt;: To put in the carved pumpkin. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking&amp;hellip; Christmas lights?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite stencil&lt;/strong&gt;: Should I go with beginner level, traditional scary face carving?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;d-day&#34;&gt;D-Day&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day has come and Now is the time. Let&amp;rsquo;s do pumpkin carving!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to admit, the day didn&amp;rsquo;t start too well. We had an appointment for Skylar&amp;rsquo;s 9-month checkup.
I got up at around 7:30am when Skylar woke up, yet again with a smile that pauses the moment
and a smile that makes me hopelessly stare at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time we walked out of the Skylar&amp;rsquo;s doctor&amp;rsquo;s office, I started to feel extremely tired as if
all those fatigue that I accumulated over the week finally decided to bring me down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there is nothing good afternoon nap can&amp;rsquo;t do. After waking up from the nap, I was ready to
rock with my pumpkins. Few emotions I had during carving pumpkins that I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt for awhile
were,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully focusing on crafting something&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building something from the ground and achieving an output&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;party-is-over&#34;&gt;Party is over&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


    
    
        
        
        
            
        
        
            
        
    

    
    
    

    
    




    
    
        
    


    

    
        &lt;span class=&#34;image left&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&#34;https://kidonchu.github.io/img/pumpkin-carving/pumpkin_carving_done.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Halloween pumpkin carving done&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;
    

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we carved Halloween pumpkins! Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;epilogue&#34;&gt;Epilogue&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You damn squirrels!&lt;/p&gt;




    
    
        
        
        
            
        
        
            
        
    

    
    
    

    
    




    
    
        
    


    

    
        &lt;span class=&#34;image left&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&#34;https://kidonchu.github.io/img/pumpkin-carving/pumpkin_carving_destroyed.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Halloween pumpkin carving destroyed&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;
    


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://kidonchu.github.io/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 07:31:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kidonchu.github.io/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;having-fun&#34;&gt;Having Fun?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The week started as normal. Just another Monday, feeling not too excited, with this irritating
thought in my head that had been lingering for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Am I having fun with my life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can go on and on about how happy I am with my lovely wife and daughter. But when the question
becomes whether I am having fun, my answer is &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working on my side projects is fun, but it has its limit. Often times, when I come home, I don&amp;rsquo;t
even turn on my laptop because of the exhaustion from the work. It&amp;rsquo;s not that the programming is not
fun; rather, my brain just gets tired out at the end of the day and no longer wants to deal with any
digital stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to freshen up, I decided to start a journal with a theme, &lt;strong&gt;SOMETHING NEW&lt;/strong&gt;. This will be the journal of
my attempts to try something new every other week, or every week if my life permits. I have no idea
what I would want to try in the next few weeks but I&amp;rsquo;m sure something will come up and I will have
plenty in my &lt;a href=&#34;https://kidonchu.github.io/todo&#34;&gt;TODO&lt;/a&gt; list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;definition-of-something-new&#34;&gt;Definition of &lt;em&gt;Something New&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are my definitions of &lt;em&gt;Something New&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Things I&amp;rsquo;ve never tried, no matter how trivial they are&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Things I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, but forgotten how I felt while doing them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Execution time is not a concern. It can be an one-day activity or something that requires weeks of
commitments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After writing all these, this idea of &lt;strong&gt;Something New&lt;/strong&gt; almost sounds like a bucket list with one
more factor added to it: emotions and feelings. &lt;em&gt;New&lt;/em&gt; in a sense that &amp;ldquo;this &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; feels new&amp;rdquo;.
This, of course, includes something I have never tried because I don&amp;rsquo;t know the feeling of something
I&amp;rsquo;ve never done before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully I can continue acting on this idea and bring fresh feelings to my life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>